I understand the situation.
Now, I just have to explain
it to the rest of the guild.
Also, we'd like a temporary
leave of absence from the guild.
Really? Why?
We have concerns with the current state
of the guild, and we need time to think.
Very well.
Although, I'm positive you won't stay
away from the battlefield for long.
Wow!
This view is amazing!
It is pretty awesome, but
don't fall off the balcony.
That would really suck.
We bought the best house.
And now we're totally broke.
It's worth it, though, because
we can live in peace here.
Kirito, what's wrong?
Well, I was thinking, does our
relationship only exist in this world?
I can't believe you'd say that.
I don't give a damn if
this is a virtual world.
My feelings for you are real.
If I learned anything in the
last two years, it's this.
To keep doing the best
we can till the very end.
And if we make it back to the real world,
I promise I'm going to find you again!
No matter what!
And fall in love with you again?
I can't believe it, I know.
I can't understand the
fact that I'm not aware of.
I'm afraid of my past.
That's it. Yeah, yeah.
Time to wait a minute, I don't like it.
I'll never be here.
If you want it, I'll never smash it.
I'll never miss you.
It's so cool that you should make it.
I'll never miss you too.
It's so cool if this is too large.
I can't read it.
No, not miss you.
I'll never miss you.
My brain is a symbol.
It's not all in your life.
L-S-A-N-S
I wanna always do it?
I'll give you everything I have!
Is he younger than me?
Kirito...
I love you.
Let's stay together forever.
Good morning, Kirito.
Morning.
Did you hear what I said?
No, I didn't hear a thing. What'd
you say? Nothing! Not a thing!
Anyway, you want to go
have some fun today?
Yeah, you know, didn't
we have fun yesterday?
And the day before, too?
So, you're saying you don't
want to go have fun today?
Wait, I know a place we can go. Come on.
Where are we going?
You're just going to have to wait
till we get there to find out.
Hey, carry me on your shoulders.
Seriously? Oh, please.
It's no fun seeing the world from
the same height all the time.
Besides, with your strength
parameter, you won't break a sweat.
Yeah, I mean, I guess, but...
Aren't you a little old for that, though?
It doesn't matter how old I am.
Come on, it's not like
anyone's gonna see us.
Okay, get on.
If you turn around, I'm gonna slap you.
Are you gonna hop on already or what?
Giddy-up!
This is so cool, you can
already see the lake from here!
No, you can see the lake, I...
Okay, if you want, you can
ride on my shoulders later!
Let's get a move on, horsey!
We're heading north-north-east!
Okay...
It almost blew up my nose!
We got people staring at us now.
Our own audience.
Come on, read back or
he'll think you're rude.
Nope, not gonna happen.
Do you want me to get off you now?
You're fine right where you are.
I heard this weird rumor
in the village yesterday.
About how if you go deep enough
into the forest, you'll see them.
See who?
Ghosts.
You mean like those in-game
astral-type monsters, right?
No, not those.
Real ghosts.
They say the tortured souls
of the monsters hunted
here come back to wander
the forest at night.
We're almost there.
The place the rumor mentions?
About a week ago, a carpenter hiked into
the forest to get some wood for a project.
He stayed so long that before
he knew it, it was night.
As he walked along, he caught a glimpse
of something white standing by a tree.
Was it a monster or something else?
The white figure slowly
walked towards some trees.
Hey, look!
I want to get down!
What's wrong with you?
It's...
it's over there!
What are you talking about?
You gotta be kidding!
Hold on.
That's not a ghost!
Wait, get it out!
Oh, jeez!
It's another player.
Yeah, but there's something
really strange about her.
What do you mean?
She doesn't have a cursor.
Maybe it's some kind of bug.
Yeah, maybe it is.
What's a little girl like
this doing playing SAO?
I guess we'll find out when she wakes up.
But we can't just leave
her out here till she does.
Let's take her home with us.
Yeah, okay.
Well, one thing's for sure.
She's not an NPC.
We didn't have any
trouble moving her here.
Yeah, that's true.
She can't be that. If she were,
she would have given off a warning when
you picked her up, like other NPCs.
You're right.
And she's definitely not
a quest giver either.
Our quest log would have been updated
as soon as we interacted with her.
She has to be a player.
She'd probably been out there for
a while, wandering around, lost.
That's the most likely scenario.
Yeah, but what was she doing out there?
Your guess is as good as mine,
but she has to have a parent
or guardian out there, right?
Mm-hmm.
She had to have logged in
with someone from her family.
I just hope they're safe.
Hey, do you think she'll wake up?
Yeah,
if her body hasn't disappeared,
that means signals are still being
transmitted to and from her nerve gear.
She's in some kind of sleep mode.
I'm sure she'll wake up soon.
And the sooner the better.
Yeah.
Hey, Kirito?
I wonder, did she log into SAO
by herself, or with her family?
Or has she been alone here, all this time?
Sleep well.
Please hurry and wake up tomorrow.
Kirito! Wake up!
Good morning.
Something wrong?
Hurry!
Get over here!
You woke up?
Thank goodness.
Do you remember what happened to you?
My name
is
Asuna,
and this is Kirito.
Try to remember.
What were you doing in the forest?
And do you know where
your mom and dad are now?
I don't know.
I can't remember anything.
Oh, no.
Well, you're awake.
Can I call you, Yui?
Mm-hmm.
Okay, then you can call me Kirito.
Can you say Kirito?
Kirito?
It's Kirito. Kirito.
That's okay.
Maybe it's a little hard.
How about you call me
whatever's easier for you?
Daddy.
Me?
Oh, nice. It's…
Mommy.
Okay, I'm Mommy. That works.
Mommy! Mommy! Daddy!
You must be hungry.
Now about breakfast. Okay.
Here you go, Yui. This one's yours
Oh, I don't know, Yui.
This one's super spicy I want
the same one that Daddy has.
Okay, if you think you're
ready for it, I won't stop you!
You only live once, right?
I like it.
Wow, you've got an iron stomach.
We can do a full course of extra
spicy food tonight if you want.
Mm-hmm.
Okay, let's not get carried away.
I'm not cooking anything nuclear.
You heard the lady.
You heard the lady?
So, what do you think?
I don't know.
She's a blank slate.
No memories.
It's really weird.
Yeah, I know.
It's like she's a baby again.
I just...
I don't...
I'm sorry.
I don't know what to do.
I get it.
You want to take care of her.
At least, until she gets her memory back.
Yeah, but...
But it's a catch-22.
We have to get back and clear the game.
Otherwise, it'll take that much
longer for Yui to be free of it.
I know.
For now, we'll do what we can.
Judging by the gear she's got in her storage,
She hasn't been out in the field much.
We'll check the Town of Beginnings.
Maybe there we can find
out if she's got family.
Okay.
Look, I don't want to say
goodbye to her either.
You really don't?
I don't know what it is.
I mean, we just met her and all.
But having her here, it's made our
little cabin feel like a real home.
Don't you think so?
Mm-hmm.
This doesn't mean we'll
never see her again.
But look, if she's got a family out there,
they're probably worried
about her right now.
Okay, when she wakes up, we'll
go to the Town of Beginnings.
That place is army territory.
It might be a good idea if we go in
fully equipped, ready for anything.
Yeah, we better be careful.
Mommy.
Daddy.
It's been forever since
I've been back here. Me too.
What do you think?
Do any of these buildings look familiar?
I don't know.
Don't get down about it.
The Town of Beginnings
is a really big place.
So how about it?
Should we start at the Central Market?
Hey, Kirito? Yeah?
Do you know how many players are here?
Right now in the town.
Hmm, good question.
Last I checked, there were 6,000
players still alive in SAO.
And about 30 % of those people, including
the army, live in the town of Beginnings.
So maybe a little less than 2,000?
Then doesn't it seem a
little dead around here?
You're right.
Leave those children alone!
Look!
It's that daycare bitch!
We've been waiting for you!
Leave them alone and let them go!
You make it sound like we're doing
something illegal, Baby Cakes.
We're just teaching them
how things work around here,
making sure they pay their way.
It's all part of the Army's job, ma 'am.
That's right.
Everyone's got to pay taxes around here.
Gin! Cait! Main! Are you okay?
Help me, Sasha! Please!
Save us!
They just want your money, so
give it to them and it'll be okay!
We tried, Teach, but they
said it's not good enough!
You know, you deadbeats owe us
a hell of a lot in back taxes.
You need to drop all the equipment you
got right there, including your armor.
Come on, honey, don't be shy.
No way!
Let me through or else!
Stand aside!
You guys are gonna be okay now?
Pick up your stuff, okay?
What the?
Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa! Hey!
Who the hell are you?
This is army business!
So get the hell out of our way!
Hold on!
I got this!
I guess you're all new in town, yeah?
Cuz we're with the the Liberation
Army, and you do not mess with us!
Kirito, take care of Yui.
Uh-huh.
What?
Oh, don't worry.
It's a safe zone.
Your HP won't deplete no matter what I do.
There's just a feeling of
getting knocked off your feet.
Even so, a fight with me is still
going to scare the hell out of you.
No, no, no!
Just stand there, you assholes!
Do something!
Ah!
Awesome!
That was so awesome!
Oh, I've never seen
anything like that before!
You are so cool!
Thank you for helping us out!
You see that?
Your mom's crazy strong, isn't she?
Their hearts...
Everyone's hearts are... Yui?
What's wrong, Yui?
Yui?
What's the matter?
Yui!
Yui, did you remember something?
I... I...
I was never here...
In this place...
I was always alone...
In the dark...
Yui!
Mommy!
I am scared!
My god.
Yui.
What was that?
I heard it so far.
It's a little sad.
It's a little sad.?
I can't do it again.
I can't
wait
for
a second time.
If I keep in mind,
there will be a hand that is all out of.
It always, once, is all out of.
Next time, Yui's Heart.